

SARAH SHIN HONNER

### **UX UI DESIGNER**

## CONTACT

+32 483 61 78 66 honnersarah@gmail.com



in www.linkedin.com/in/sarahhonner

• www.flickr.com/photos/sarahhonner

## **PROFILE**

I'm a cosmopolitan born and raised in sunny Los Angeles, California. I am a firm believer that my diverse educational and professional experience coupled with my international ventures strengthen my understanding of and interactions with users across the board and bring a fresh perspective to my UX work.

Some of my hobbies and interests include photography, reading, traveling, learning languages, meeting new people, and outdoor activities (but I also enjoy being a couch potato).

Fun fact: I have mild trypophobia

#### LANGUAGES

**ENGLISH** Native KOREAN Native FRENCH B2 SPANISH B2

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2018 - 2019

#### **CAREERFOUNDRY**

UX Design certification Specialization in UI Design Specialization in Front End Development

### 2014 - 2015

## KATHOLIEKE UNIVERSITEIT LEUVEN (KU LEUVEN)

European Studies: Transnational and Global Perspectives M.A.

#### 2012 - 2013

# UNIVERSIDAD COMPLUTENSE DE MADRID

Study abroad program - Psychology courses

### 2010 - 2014

# UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, LOS ANGELES (UCLA)

Psychology B.A.

International Development Studies B.A.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### SEPTEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2018

#### CHRISTIAN SOLIDARITY WORLDWIDE

# Advocacy and Research Assistant

Conducted research and EU advocacy for a human rights organization specializing in the right to freedom of religion or belief (FoRB), for people of all faiths. Represented religious minorities in countries across Africa, the Middle Fast, South and East Asia and Latin America.

## JUNE 2016 - FEBRUARY 2017

### MY REFUGE HOUSE

# Communications and Community Outreach Intern

Developed and solidified My Refuge House's online and offline presence by creating engaging marketing materials and social media presence (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Blog).

## FEBRUARY 2016 - APRIL 2016

# KIC EUROPE

# **Business Development Intern**

Worked on two ongoing projects, Startup Autobahn and Kstartup Challenge, to bridge and foster the startup ecosystems in Europe and South Korea.

#### **SKILLS & TOOLS**

- Agile/Lean process
- UX research
- User personas/flow/mapping Invision
- Information architecture
- Usability testing
- Wireframing & prototyping
- Visual design
- Responsive design

- Sketch
- · Affinity Designer
- Balsamiq
- Principle
- Adobe XD
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript